嘿 大家好 这里是NASASpaceflight的Jack Beyer
Hey everyone. Jack Beyer here for NASASpaceflight.
欢迎来到我们的第一个博卡奇卡每周更新
Welcome to our first Boca Chica weekly update.
随着这么多事儿发生在了SpaceX的南德克萨斯设施
With so much going on at SpaceX's South Texas facilities,
原作者名：NASASpaceflight
视频来源：youtu.be/aJrJQddXxGM
原视频发布日期：20200711
字幕翻译/压制：旋火
我们希望用更好的方式让大家了解Starship的进展情况
We wanted a better way for everyone to keep track of what's going on the Starship progress.
所以我们决定除了每天的视频之外 还做这些每周更新的视频
So we decided to do these weekly update videos in addition to our daily videos.
如果你有什么建议 请在评论中告诉我们你的想法
Let us know what you think in the comments if you have any suggestion.
当然也要感谢Mary又名Boca Chica女孩儿让这一切成为可能
And of course thanks as always to Mary aka Boca Chica gal for making all this possible.
不再废话了 让我们直奔主题
Without any further fuss let's get into it.
巨大的马尼托瓦克18000起重机又名蓝色怪物开始运转了
The massive Manitowoc 18,000 crane aka Bluezilla came online
并开始建造新的大厂房 将用于堆叠组装Super Heavy
and began building the new high bay which will be used for stacking Super Heavy.
与中厂房相比 这里进度快得惊人
Progress is going into sanely fast compared to the Mid Bay.
大块的墙体在被吊到位之前就已经在地面上预装好了
With large wall segments being pre-built on the ground before being lifted into place.
按照这个速度 我们应该很快就能看到大厂房完工
At this speed, we should see the high bay completed in no time.
接下来是通过低温压力测试的Starship SN5
Next, Starship SN5 having passed the cryo pressure test.
已经安装了一台猛禽发动机
We've got a Raptor installed.
确切地说 是猛禽SN27
Raptor SN27 to be exact.
在静态火力测试前的一周 仍在持续准备航天器 新引擎和发射台
We're prepping the vehicle, its new engines and the launchpad continues all week ahead of static fire testing.
目前预计不会早于7月13日
Currently expected no earlier than July 13th.
就像SN4一样 SN5也已经装上了配重也就是机头球杆 以更好地模拟实际飞行力学状态
Just like SN4, SN5 has been filled with a mass simulator aka nose cue to better simulate actual flight dynamics.
我们预计静态火力测试将采用单引擎配置
We're expecting a single engine configuration for static fire testing
如果一切顺利 就能最终实现150米的跳跃
and if all goes well and an eventual 150 meter hop.
由于该单发动机将偏离载具的中心
Since that single engine will be offset from the center of the vehicle,
起飞时 它的发动机偏移的推力将使其偏离发射台
it will pretty much power slide off the pad.
马一龙在Twitter上确认 一个引擎的飞行会看起来有点奇怪
Elon confirming that one engine flight will look a little odd on Twitter.
下一艘Starship原型机的新部分已经被移入中厂房 与SN6一起堆放
New sections for the next Starship prototype have been moved into the Mid Bay for stacking alongside SN6.
我们不知道这个储罐是否还在使用301不锈钢 还是其过渡到304L
We don't know if this tankage is still using 301 stainless steel or if its transition to 304L.
我们也不知道它被分配给了哪台SN Starship
And we don't know what serial number has been assigned to it.
我们过去看到过304L写在环上
We've seen 304L written on rings in the past.
所以将来可能会弄清楚这是哪种类型
So it might be possible to figure out which type this is in the future
如果我们能拍到一些环的特写
if we get some good close-ups of the ring.
有人没关鼻锥制造机
Someone left the nose cone machine on.
还有三个鼻锥放在制造帐篷外面
Dang it Earl and there's still three nose cones sitting around outside the fabrication tents.
这就难说了
it's hard to say
他们的试制鼻锥是为了练习制造技术还是实际的飞行硬件？
whether their Pathfinder nose cones meant to practice manufacturing techniques or actual flight hardware
或它们是由什么类型的钢制成的
or what type of steel they're made out of.
较新的鼻锥看起来在设计过程中更进一步 安装了RCS推进器和一些端口
The newer nose cones look to be further along in the design process with RCS thrusters and a few ports installed.
本周发生了几起值得注意的交付事件
Several notable deliveries occurred this week.
储罐场的新储罐
New tanks for the tank farm.
一些未知的金属部件
Some unknown metal parts.
一个新的食品拖车
A new food trailer.
几个未知类型的不锈钢卷
A several stainless steel rolls of unknown type.
第一次非常近距离地看到了机器狗宙斯
Very spotted Zeus the Robo dog up close for the first time,
照片和视频显示其包含29000美元的检查套装
providing these photos and videos of it in the $29,000 inspection package fitted with.
检查套装包括360度摄像头
The inspection package includes 360-degree camera,
30倍光学变焦的摇摄 倾斜 缩放摄像机
a PTZ camera with 30 times optical zoom,
加上通过扬声器和麦克风播放和录制音频的能力
plus the ability to play and record audio via speakers and a microphone.
Super Heavy发射场的建造工作持续进行着
Work at the launch site continue it with progress on the Super Heavy launchpad.
以及Starship亚轨道发射架及其地面支持设备
On the Starship suborbital launch mount and its ground support equipment.
还有Starship着陆台附近的地面工作
On the earth work near the Starship landing pad.
而在Starship着陆台附近的神秘施工正继续着
And mystery construction continue near the Starship pad.
在发射场挂了几个星期的SN3终于被完全切割成了碎片
After hanging out at the launch site for weeks SN3 was finally cut to pieces and all the way.
博卡奇卡的那些工地周围的进度继续让人印象深刻
The pace around those sites at Boca Chica continues to impress
尽管马上就要集中进行SN5静态火力测试的活动了
ahead of the switch and focus to SN5 static fire test campaign.
希望如果静态火力测试顺利的话 我们会看到它尝试进行150米的跳跃
Hopefully if a static fire testing goes well we will see it attempt a 150 meter hop.
再次感谢Mary记录了所有这些不可思议的事件
Thanks again to Mary for documenting all of these incredible events.
请随时在评论中提供你对这种新的每周总结形式的反馈
Please feel free to provide your feedback on this new weekly round-up format in the comments.
记得通过订阅 点赞和成为会员来支持这个频道
Remember to support the channel by subscribing liking and becoming a member
跟上博卡奇卡的日更视频
to keep up with the daily videos from Boca Chica.
谢谢你的观看
Thanks for watching.
祝好
Be excellent to each other.